{
	"data": [
		{
			"id": "1000",
			"name": "Quiz demo 1",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "10001",
					"question": "How many fingers do you have",
					"answer": "Five"
				},
				{
					"id": "10002",
					"question": "What is the name of your planet",
					"answer": "Earth"
				},
				{
					"id": "10003",
					"question": "What is the result of 1+1",
					"answer": "Two"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": "2000",
			"name": "Quiz demo 2",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "20001",
					"question": "How many fingers do you have",
					"answer": "Five"
				},
				{
					"id": "20002",
					"question": "What is the name of your planet",
					"answer": "Earth"
				},
				{
					"id": "20003",
					"question": "What is the result of 1+1",
					"answer": "Two"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": "3000",
			"name": "Quiz demo 3",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "30001",
					"question": "How many fingers do you have",
					"answer": "Five"
				},
				{
					"id": "30002",
					"question": "What is the name of your planet",
					"answer": "Earth"
				},
				{
					"id": "30003",
					"question": "What is the result of 1+1",
					"answer": "Two"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": "4000",
			"name": "Quiz demo 4",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "40001",
					"question": "How many fingers do you have",
					"answer": "Five"
				},
				{
					"id": "40002",
					"question": "What is the name of your planet",
					"answer": "Earth"
				},
				{
					"id": "40003",
					"question": "What is the result of 1+1",
					"answer": "Two"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": "5000",
			"name": "Quiz demo 5",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "50001",
					"question": "How many fingers do you have",
					"answer": "Five"
				},
				{
					"id": "50002",
					"question": "What is the name of your planet",
					"answer": "Earth"
				},
				{
					"id": "50003",
					"question": "What is the result of 1+1",
					"answer": "Two"
				}
			]
		}
	]
}
